hey i just wanted to remind you that you're not alone like even when you're physically alone
you're not alone you know and and i think sometimes we really um we get really lost
in that feeling and nothing you're doing is ever truly alone i know some of y'all are like no no
no i'm really over here doing this by myself and as somebody who's really doing stuff by myself i
really relate to that i also then have to remember how many folks even if they just said a sentence to
me helped give me a boost of energy to keep doing the thing that i'm doing like with my album i have
to say that my homeboys really showed up like my engineer matt cody my producer ray angry who didn't
even produce on this project just always pours so much love and belief and encouragement and
encouragement into me my boy barry who i'd give an early preview we call it an early preview because
he's bayesian they always put two words together they're the same word like a bullco or exactly
precisely my bayesian accent is still working but every time i would send him a record he would
listen to it and he would give me this like very deeply thought out response that would let me be
able to like precisely consider what i needed to change or not change or where it fits in the whole
project my homeboy rich rocca you know it's like i could just send him a song at any time a day
well i'm old so i don't really have to be that late but he gonna listen to it and he's gonna text
me back with some form of encouragement that is not something to be taken lightly they didn't have to
be here shooting with me in the gym they didn't have to be here buying me equipment none of that
to play integral roles in my being able to continue the mission that i was on so for everybody out there
who really just feels totally alone in your mission i want to also remind you that sometimes
the companionship in that process is not going to come from someone you know
it might come from a complete stranger just being that glimmer of kindness that day
it might come from your animals it might come from your tree
just know that we can't ever really be alone when we're all connected and by all i mean
the plants the animals and us cut out the corporate middlemen and purchase my music directly from me
head to amandadiva.bandcamp.com and pay whatever price you want for truth translator this ain't a
movement it's movement music